Emerson, Lynn, Industrial Education Files /4092
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lynn Emerson Industrial Education Files
1934-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Emerson, Lynn
/4092
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3086341
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4297: ILR School Biography Files
Emerson, Lynn Arthur,1890-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3086341
- I-131 Seminar in Industrial Educ., 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Binghamton - X30 Technical Inst. Educ. - Development and (non credit) Philosophy, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- List of Students who have Received Degrees with Major in Industrial Education Since ILR School Took Over Industrial Education, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Block, Herman H., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- John Byrd Extra-Mural (Box 1, Folder 5)
- H. Kenneth Brooks S.S., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Frank S. Bull, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Vincent Davies, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dormeyer, John Emil, 1938-1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Anthony Ekes Extra-Mural, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Feng, Chao Hwa (Minor), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Filmer, Floyd F., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Frederick, Dean M. (MS in Ed), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Kenneth K. French, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ganter, Charles F., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dominic Giambo Extra-Mural (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Gruen, Karl C. Minor, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Hobbie, Richard H., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Hordes, Samuel, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Horace N. Hubbs, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Jyding, Dagny Alice (Advisor), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Kana, Raymond W., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Krum, Earl E., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- McClain, James William, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- John E. McCullough, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Sherman Mears, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Michael F. Nealis, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- O'Toole, Christopher, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Harold W. Payne, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Perkins, Belford A., 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Peters, Irving John, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Peterson, Robert R., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Powers, James D., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Ramage, Raymond, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ruhland, Paul M., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Roth, Alfred Cyrus, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Shepherd, Marshall, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Stanat, Arthur E., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Drew, Everett C., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Gorman, Thomas Harty, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Jones, Merwin Miller, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Kindinger, Edward P., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Langer, Elmer B., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Gavett, J. W. (Minor), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Hubben, Herbert (Minor), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Hughes, Arthur J. (Minor), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Kolaja, Jiri Thomas (Minor) (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Badore, Darrell H., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Maher, Patricia B. MILR, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Van Schaack, Herbert (Minor), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Diamond, Anthony T., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Lawrence, Lois C. (Minor), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Colt, James Paul (Minor), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Moore, James - Minor, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- List of Students who have Received Degrees with Major in Industrial Education Prior to 1947 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Avery, John M., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Beach, C. Kenneth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Bensman, Clarence H. (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Caplan, Morris, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Coyle, Frank J., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Dixon, Clarence R., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Finsterbach, Thomas W., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Gifford, Gordon E., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Hamilton, Edward H. (Minor), 1948 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Hesse, Alexander N., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Jacobsen, Eckhart A., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Johnson, Walfred John, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Klitgord, Otto, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Lambert, James H., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Lynds, Murray D., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- McTaggart, Arthur J., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Nechanicky, Blanche B., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Neff, Arthur William, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Perkins, Roy B. (Minor), 1952 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Pierson, Edward M., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Ranney, Harold W., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Rogers, William W., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Schimel, Abraham L., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Van Oot, James M., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- R. J. Sitte Lee, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Potential Candidates for Graduate Study, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- ILR - 699, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- I-631 Seminar Ind. Educ. Summer 1954 SS (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Human Problems in Quality Control NCR and Mach. Union, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- I-530 Indust. Education Spring 1954 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- I-530 Indust. Education Spring 1954 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- I-590 Written Commun. Spring 1954 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- I-590 Written Communication Fall 1953 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- I-333 Devel. Of Written Instimatls Fall 1953 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- I-633 Devel. Of Written Inst. Materials Fall 1953 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Ext. Course Herman Problems in Spoon Spring 1953 Ithaca Mgmt. Club (Box 1, Folder 91)
- I 530 Inpost. Educ. Spring 1953 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- I-192 Ind. Occup. And Processes Spring 1953 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- I-192 Ind. Occup. And Processes Spring 1953 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- General Electric Johnson City Human Problems in Supervision, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Devel. Written Instr. Materials Fall 1952 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- A-2436 Seminar in SS 1941 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- A-243 Admin. Of SS 1941 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- N.Y.U. - Research in Doc. Ed. 131:73 Fast 1940 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- N.Y.U. - Research in Voc. Educ. 1948 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- N.Y.U. - Spring 1941 Dev. Of Instr. Material (Box 1, Folder 101)
- N.Y.U. - Fall 1940 Curric. Const. (Box 1, Folder 102)
- A-243 Admin. Of Ind. And Tech. Ed. Summer Session, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- A 242a Seminar in Ind. Arts Education (Admin. And Sprn.), 1945 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- R. E. 246 Problems in Ind. And Tech. Educ. Spring Term 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- R.E. 246 Probs. In Indus. And Tech. Education Fall Term 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- RE 145 Curriculum Building in Industrial Schools Extra-Mural Rochester 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- A-31 Studies in Educational and Occupational Opportunities Summer Session 1939 (Voss) (Box 1, Folder 108)
- A-243 Problems in the Administration of Industrial and Technical Education Summer Session, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- R. E. 246 Probs. In Ind. And Tech. Ed. Spring Term, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- R.E. 246 Probs. In Ind. And Tech. Ed. Fall Term, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- A 243c Problems in Ind. And Tech. Educ. Extra-Mural Rochester, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- A 28 Educ. And Vocational Guidance 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- A 243 Adm. Of Ind, and Tech. Educ. Summer Session, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- A 243 Adm. Of Ind. And Tech. Educ. Summer Session, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- State-- Development of Instr. Mat'l. for Ind. And Tech. Schools Yonkers, Spring, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- A 243 Adm. Of Ind. And Tech. Educ. Summer Session, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- A-243b Seminar in Vocational Industrial and Technical Education Summer Session, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- A 243b Seminar in Ind. And Tech. Ed. Summer Session, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- A 29 Anal. Of Individual and Counseling Summer Session, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- A 31 Educ. And Occup. Information Summer Session, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- A 28 Educ. And Vocational Guidance. Summer Session, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- A 31 Educ. And Occup. Information Summer Session, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- State 296a Educ. And Vocational Guidance. N.Y.C., Spring, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- State 296a Educ. And Vocational Guidance N.Y.C. Fall 1937 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- State 296a Educ. And Vocational. Guidance N.Y.C. Spring 1937 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- A 28 Educ. And Vocational Guidance Summer Session, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- A 28a Educ. And Vocational Guidance. Summer Session, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- State 296a Educ. And Vocational Guidance N.Y.C. Fall, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Oswego - Summer Session 1934 - Org. 8 Teaching of did. And Tech. Ed, Course 55 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- I-199 Special Studies, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- B-300 Research, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- IBM - Dev. Of Mat'l. 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- IBM - 1941 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- IBM - 1940 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- I-896 Curriculum Workshop - Tech Inst. Summer Sess. 1948 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- I-80 Devel. And Organ. Of Ind. Ed. Fall '48-'49, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- I-84 Appraisal, Use and Devel. Of Instructional Materials Fall '48-'49, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- I-84 Appraisal, Use and Devel. Of Instructional Materials. Fall 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 139)